#### Contact

Mumbai 7208444692 (Mobile) d\_gurbux@yahoo.com

www.linkedin.com/in/gurubux-gill (LinkedIn)

github.com/Gurubux (Other) gurubux.wordpress.com/ (Blog) stackoverflow.com/story/gurubuxgill (Portfolio)

## Top Skills

Java

Liferay

Hibernate

#### Certifications

Structuring Machine Learning Projects

Python 101 for Data Science

Applied Data Science with Python - Level 2

Data Visualization with Python

Learning Python: Rapid Training 2019 | The Ultimate Guide to Python 3.7.2

# Gurubux Gill

Software Developer. Microsoft certified in Python. Aspiring Data scientist, Machine learning & Deep learning developer.

Mumbai, Maharashtra, India

# Summary

BE Graduate, 3 years of experience as a Software Developer(Java). Microsoft Certified in Python with relevant knowledge in data preprocessing, analysis and visualization. Currently pursuing full-time research through MOOCs and seeking Job/internship opportunities in Data science, Machine Learning and Deep Learning algorithms and frameworks. Posses keen interest in learning and applying knowledge using the cutting edge tools in the data overloaded world to facilitate business insights, research and build models, staying updated to state-of-the art technologies and make a worthwhile impact in the society.

# Experience

LA TECHNOLOGIES LTD

Senior Software Developer July 2018 - January 2019 (7 months)

Mumbai Area, India

Client Adani Power, earlier Reliance Power. Developing Liferay Portal contents, custom portlets, web services, Portlet Service with Java as the base language and ES6, HTML5, CSS. Handling LiferayMySql and external Oracle database. Liferay Content management of the Production site using the admin panel. Deployment of modules on QA and production servers, tomcat. Coordinating with the branding team as per the the website change from Reliance to Adani.

MindCraft Software Pvt. Ltd.

Consultant

February 2016 - June 2018 (2 years 5 months)

Software development on Liferay Framework to develop Portal using Java, JavaScript, jQuery, ajax, css and aui-scripting.

Education

### St. Francis Institute Of Technology

Bachelor of Engineering (BE), Computer Engineering · (2012 - 2015)

# freeCodeCamp

Full Stack Web Development Certification, Computer Software Engineering · (2016 - 2017)

### Sardar Vallabhbhai patel Polytechnic

High School Diploma, Computer Engineering · (2009 - 2012)